[{"answer": "I don't know, but I'm hoping somewhere nice.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 8, "question": "Wow, where do we go from here?", "qSentId": 7}, {"answer": "Well, it's actually very, very -- well, the idea came to me last week, actually, about a week ago, that I should -- that I should, perhaps, kind of express my happiness at this marriage in a way publicly.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "What gave you the idea for this?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Yes, I met Charles a few times.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Although, I don't know Charles, you know?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Only through a mutual friend who gave me -- I gave him the name of the song that I was going to sing and asked him at least to run it by them.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "George, I mean, have you had any contact with the palace in relation this song that you've done?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "George, obviously, the whole world will be watching this wedding in a couple weeks.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "You know, if they're genuinely happy for these two people, which I think a lot of people are, you know?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "I think -- I think it -- well, there are two things about this wedding.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "What do you think it means for Britain and indeed for the royal family to have such global attention?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "What about you?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Oh, I think she probably would have thought there was no woman good enough for her son, probably like most women.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "What do you think she would have made of Kate, who obviously she never got a chance to meet?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Yes, I think so.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "But I think she probably would have loved her, wouldn't she?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Yes, I think she seems very sweet.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "She seems a very sweet girl, doesn't she?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Oh, I think they should -- I don't think they need any advice from me.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "I mean, what kind of message would you give to them on the big day when it comes up?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "I don't know, but I'm hoping somewhere nice.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Wow, where do we go from here?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Yes, because you're the one who put the \"sex\" in \"Sex in the City.\"", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Oh, I do?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Well, we look similar.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "How similar are you?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Well, I'm sort of a serial monogamist.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "In what way?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "Well, I think that I fall in love.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "So, how have you managed to be monogamous in an era when it's so unfashionable?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Well, I --", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "You are intimidating to men, just purely from this character, aren't you?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Interesting.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "And how are you finding British men?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Well, I'm -- I like men around my age.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "So, if there are any single, good-looking guys, what kind of age range would you prefer?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "No, no, no, no.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Samantha would never do that, would she?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Well, I've written two books, one with -- for couples about sex, and it was about communication more than anything else.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "You've written books about sex, haven't you?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "You always have guests coming in.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Excuse me?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's -- it's not as easy as it looks.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "What have you learned about marriage and sex and relationships over the years, do you think?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "I felt that -- I did compromise a lot at the beginning.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Do you feel that you've had to compromise in your private life?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Yes, I do, to an extent.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Do you remain romantic about marriage?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Some ways.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Do you regret that?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I got 20 bucks.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Is never a good time?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Fantastic.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "How do you put on the weight?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "You can eat whatever the hell you want and you can have as much of it.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Eat donuts?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "As I said to a friend of mine, it was heaven putting it on.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "How many seconds did it take you to lose the weight once the movie finished?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I love it.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Do you like being in your 50s?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Because I know who I am.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "I am -- I'm Kim.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Who are you?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "I think she's a woman in her 50s who's had a terrific, terrific career and has been, you know, very fulfilled in that and has been courageous and strong and lonely sometimes and crazy sometimes and very insecure and also very confident.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Who is Kim?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Can be, yes.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Has that led to moments when you felt -- has it been occasionally -- you hinted at it -- being lonely, being the real woman behind Samantha?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "So he was in the navy?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "And he wasn't a hero?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "To me, again, it's script driven.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Would you like to?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "I don't know where this comes from.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Are you all still mates or do you all hate each other?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I would very much like to continue the road that I'm on, which is, you know, playing parts.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "If I can interview in five years time, what would you like to have happened to you in the next five years?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "ATTRALL: I'd definitely like to be in a relationship and -- with someone who gets what I do and is, you know, supportive and behind what I've always been doing, which is following my heart's desire, which is to work as an actor.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Where would you like to be in five years?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Well, no, to be perfect -- to be totally truthful, which I tend to like to be, I had this idea initially, but I thought that one, maybe they wouldn't like the idea, so I wanted something else as I =-- because I hadn't recorded anything yet.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Have you based your final decision on a suggestion that came that way?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "That's a completely different level.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "Is it a particular pressure that only the kids of famous people understand?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "Oh, amazing.", "docId": "110415pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "For her, who has just come into this family, just like Diana, huge pressure, isn't it?", "qSentId": 572}]